[♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Mommy Pig and Daddy Pig
have a new picture
of Peppa and George.
We should put this lovely
new picture on the wall.
Leave it to me.
I am the DIY expert
of the house.
Are you sure
you can do it?
Of course.
I'll just put
a nail in the wall
and hang the picture
on it.
Very good. I'm just off to visit
Granny and Grandpa Pig.
I'll see you later.
[ENGINE STARTS]
And please
don't make a mess.
[LAUGHS]
Mess?
Goodbye.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
ALL: Goodbye.
[LAUGHS]
Daddy, can we help
put up the picture?
You can watch, and then you'll
learn how to do it properly.
First, I need
a tape measure.
And a pencil.
[SNORTS]
That is where
I'm going to put the nail.
Don't break the wall,
Daddy.
[LAUGHS]
DADDY PIG:
Now I need a hammer and a nail.
Stand back, children,
and watch a craftsman at work.
Daddy Pig is going to knock
the nail into the wall.
[SNORTS]
Don't break the wall,
Daddy.
[LAUGHS]
Don't be silly, Peppa.
[SNORTS]
Easy as pie.
Oh, it's not meant
to do that.
Daddy Pig has made
a big crack in the wall.
Oh, Daddy.
You've broken the wall.
It's just a tiny crack.
The picture will hide it.
There.
I can still see
the crack, Daddy.
Yes, I'll just take the nail out
and fill in the crack.
Don't make a mess, Daddy.
[LAUGHS]
Don't be silly, Peppa.
[GRUNTS]
It's coming out.
Whoa!
Oh, Daddy.
Now you really
have broken the wall.
Hmm.
Do you think Mommy
will notice?
Uh, yes, I think
she might.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Quick, George.
What are they doing?
[SNORTING]
Daddy, we can see you.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Hmm.
Daddy Pig
has to mend the wall
before Mommy Pig
comes home.
DADDY PIG:
Brick, please.
First, Daddy Pig fills the hole
with bricks.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
There.
[BOTH SNICKER]
Next, Daddy Pig puts plaster
over the bricks.
[LAUGHS]
Easy as pie.
Then Daddy Pig
paints the wall.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Good as new.
The wall is mended.
Hooray!
[BOTH LAUGH]
But look at all the mess
they have made.
Goodness me.
We had better clean up
before Mommy comes back.
First, Daddy pig quickly washes
Peppa and George.
Then Peppa
vacuums the floor.
And Daddy Pig
tidies up the tools.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
[GASPS]
Mommy.
Mommy Pig is home.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
Mommy!
[GASPS]
Mommy's here.
Quick, pretend nothing
has happened.
[SNORTS]
Hello.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
What have you been doing?
Oh, nothing.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Yes, I can see
you've been doing nothing.
I thought you were going
to put the picture up.
In all the excitement,
Daddy Pig has forgotten
to put the picture up.
Oh.
Well, I'm no expert,
but I'm sure
it's quite easy.
[SNORTS]
There.
Hmm, yes, that did look
quite easy.
But when you did it, Daddy,,
it looked really hard.
Shush, Peppa.
Don't tell anyone.
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her family
are going to the beach.
Peppa and George
love going to the beach.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
What a lot of stuff.
We must be careful not to forget
anything when we go.
Sunshade, beach bag,
towels,
buckets and spades,
and a spotty ball.
Good. Now, before you start
playing,
you need some
sun cream on you.
The sun is very hot,
so Peppa and George
have to have sun cream on.
Let's try out
this spotty ball.
It seems to work.
[CHUCKLES]
What a great spotty ball.
[BOTH LAUGH]
George, you throw the ball,
and I will catch it.
[GIGGLES AND SNORTS]
George, catch.
Oh, dear. George is too little
to catch the ball.
[CRIES]
Never mind, George.
Would you and Peppa like to have
a paddle in the sea?
Yes, please, Daddy.
[SNORTING]
Let's put your water wings on.
[BLOWING]
There we go.
You look very smart
in your water wings, George.
[LAUGHS]
My turn. My turn.
[BLOWS]
Good.
[LAUGHS]
Now we can play
in the Water.
Hooray!
[BOTH GIGGLE]
[SNORTS]
Is the water cold?
It's lovely
and warm.
Aah!
[LAUGHS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Steady on.
You started it,
Daddy Pig.
Maybe that's enough
splashing.
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
Whee!
Daddy, I love being
at the beach.
Peppa and George
love the beach.
Everyone loves the beach.
MOMMY PIG:
Peppa, George.
Would you like to play
with your buckets and spades?
Yes, please, Mommy.
Daddy. Daddy.
Can we bury you
in the sand?
Uh, well...
Please, Daddy.
Oh, all right.
Yippee!
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa and George are burying
Daddy Pig in the sand.
Steady on.
[ALL LAUGH]
There.
Now you can't escape.
My head is getting
a bit hot.
Can I have
my straw hat?
Well, if you say "please."
Please can I have
my straw hat?
Yes, you may, Daddy.
[GIGGLES]
[SNORTS]
That's nice.
[YAWNS]
Maybe I'll just have
a little sleep.
[SNORES]
[BOTH LAUGH]
George, let's make
sand castles.
Peppa and George
are making sand castles.
First we put sand
in the buckets.
Like this.
We turn the buckets upside down
and tap them.
And lift the bucket up.
Hey, presto.
A sand castle.
[SNORTS]
Hey, presto.
Another sand castle.
MOMMY PIG:
Peppa, George.
Home time.
Don't leave
any stuff behind.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Let's check that we haven't
forgotten anything.
Towels, beach bag,
sunshade,
and the spotty ball.
That's everything.
I'm sure we've forgotten
something.
Hmm.
[SNORTS]
[LAUGHS]
Of course.
We forgot the hat.
[SNORTS]
[SNORING]
PEPPA:
Daddy!
We forgot Daddy!
Oh, yes!
We forgot Daddy Pig.
Huh? What?
Daddy, we almost
left you behind.
But George remembered you.
[SNORTS]
[LAUGHS]
Well, I'm glad
George remembered me.
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is playing
with her doll's house.
George is playing too.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Peppa making a tea party
for the doll family.
[SNORTS]
Here, George.
I'm the mommy and daddy.
You can be the children.
[LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
Children.
It's nearly tea time,
so you must wash your hands.
[SNORTING]
George is putting
the dolls to bed.
Night night.
George, why are you putting
the children to bed?
They're having
a tea party.
George likes putting
the dolls to bed.
Children, come down stairs right
now or you won't get any cake.
George isn't listening.
He's too busy
putting the dolls to bed.
George, if you want to play
with my doll's house,
you have to help
with the tea party.
Here, George, you can fill
the teapot with water.
[SNORTS]
Children, come downstairs
right now.
Mommy, we're coming.
[LAUGHS]
George is going to fill
the teapot with water.
Ooh.
George has found a spider
in the sink.
[LAUGHS]
George wants the spider
to be his friend.
Oh.
[GIGGLES]
George likes the spider.
The spider likes George.
[LAUGHS]
Peppa loves playing
tea parties.
[LAUGHING]
Where are all the chocolate
biscuits, Daddy?
We had lots yesterday.
Oh, I'm sorry, Mommy.
I must have eaten them all.
Ho, ho, ho.
[LAUGHS]
Naughty daddy.
George is putting
the spider to bed.
Night night.
George, what are you doing?
You have to help me
with the tea party.
[SCREAMS]
Help! Help!
Daddy! There's a spider
in my bedroom!
Oh, don't worry, Peppa.
Please, Daddy,
take it away.
[LAUGHING]
No need to panic.
Hello, George.
Have you seen the spider?
[SNORTS]
It's too scary.
Take it away.
There's no need
to be afraid, Peppa.
[SNORTS]
Spiders are very,
very small,
and they can't hurt you.
But don't worry.
Daddy will take it
out of the bedroom.
Whoa!
He's quite big,
isn't he?
Um, I'll just fetch
Mommy Pig.
Mommy Pig!
[LAUGHS]
Hello, Mr. Skinnylegs.
Peppa feels
a little bit braver.
He likes being
in my doll's house.
Hello, children, I hear
you've found a little spider.
I'll take him out the bedroom
so you two can play.
Mommy, his name
is Mr. Skinnylegs.
Aah! Mr. Skinnylegs
is big, isn't he?
[PEPPA AND GEORGE GIGGLE]
Peppa and George
like the spider.
[SNORTING]
Night night.
George is putting
the spider to bed.
No, George!
He wants some tea.
He doesn't want
to be in bed.
Are you hungry,
Mr. Skinnylegs?
Would you like some cake?
Peppa isn't afraid
of the spider anymore.
Mommy, Daddy, sit down.
We are all going to have tea
with Mr. Skinnylegs.
[SNORTS]
Who wants tea?
Me, please.
[SNORTS]
Delicious.
Peppa loves playing
tea parties.
[LAUGHS]
Here's your tea, Mr. Skinnylegs.
What's that?
You want to say hello
to my daddy?
Hello, Mr. Daddy Pig.
Uh, that's all right, Peppa.
Let Mr. Skinnylegs
drink his tea.
You're not scared,
are you, Daddy?
Oh, no, of course not.
Aah! Not so close.
[LAUGHS]
Whoa!
[GASPS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa likes Mr. Skinnylegs.
Everyone likes
Mr. Skinnylegs.
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig
are taking Peppa and George out
for a day on the river.
Welcome aboard,
me hearties.
[SNORTS]
Peppa, George.
Let's put
your life jackets on.
When Peppa and George
are on Grandpa Pig's boat,
they must wear life jackets.
On this boat,
I'm the captain.
Aye, aye, captain.
[SNORTS]
When Captain Grandpa
tells you all to do something,
you must do it.
[WHISPERING]
Unless it's something silly.
Captain Grandpa
never says anything silly.
Of course not,
Captain Grandpa.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
George, raise the flag.
[SNORTING]
Peppa, ring the bell.
Aye, aye, captain.
[CLANGING]
Granny Pig,
take the wheel.
Aye, aye, captain.
Full sail.
[MOTOR REVS]
[SNORTS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
[QUACKING]
Maybe you should go
a little slower, Grandpa Pig.
Good idea, Granny Pig.
I don't want to use up
all my petrol.
Grandpa, I liked it
when we went fast.
Don't worry, Peppa,
we'll go fast later.
[SNORTS]
Look!
There's another boat.
Here's Granddad Dog.
He's taking Danny Dog out
for a day on the river.
Ahoy there,
Granddad Dog!
Grandpa Pig!
Hello, Danny.
[BELL CLANGS]
Hello, Peppa.
[HORN TOOTS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Granddad Dog is Grandpa Pig's
very best friend.
[LAUGHS]
I'm surprised your boat
is still afloat, Granddad Dog.
It must be almost as old
as you are.
[BARKS]
This old boat
can go faster
than your rusty bucket
any day, Grandpa Pig.
All right, you old sea dog,
race you.
Prepare to lose,
water hog.
[SNORTING]
[BARKING]
You two are acting like
little children.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Granddad Dog called me
a water hog.
You called him a sea dog first,
Grandpa.
You should say sorry.
Only if he says
sorry first.
Granddad, say sorry
to Grandpa Pig.
He is your best friend.
No. He's a water hog,
and my boat is faster than his.
All right, sea dog.
Let's race
to the next bridge.
On the count of three!
One, two...
Go!
You started too soon.
Catch me if you can,
water hog!
[BARKS]
Sea dog!
[SNORTS]
Is that as fast
as you can go?
[SNORTS]
Can't catch me!
[LAUGHS]
I win!
[ENGINE SPUTTERS]
Oh, dear.
Grandpa Pig's boat
has run out of petrol.
Very clever,
Captain Grandpa.
Maybe I did go
a bit too fast.
How will we get home?
Look, there's Granddad Dog.
[HORN TOOTS]
Granddad Dog
can tow us home.
I'm not being towed
by that sea dog.
I haven't offered
to tow the water hog.
[SIGHS]
Will you two
ever grow up?
Grandpa, say sorry
to Granddad Dog.
I'm sorry I called you
a sea dog.
Granddad, say sorry
to Grandpa Pig.
I'm sorry I called you
a water hog.
That's nice.
Granddad Dog, would you be
so kind as to tow us home?
It would be my pleasure, madame!
Catch this, captain.
Aye, aye, skipper.
Granddad Dog is Grandpa Pig's
very best friend.
[SNORTS]
[BARKS]
Granddad Dog is towing
Grandpa Pig's boat home.
The main thing is,
I won the race.
Grandpa Pig!
Naughty Grandpa Pig.
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa, ring the bell.
Aye, aye,
Captain Grandpa.
[BELL CLANGS]
[HORN TOOTS]
[PEPPA LAUGHING AND SNORTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING AND LAUGHING]